ATHM Textile Industry Cloth Labels 6524/003 MB
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ATHM Textile Industry Cloth Labels
1830-1976
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
6524/003 MB
6.44 cubic feet
6.3 linear ft.
.
Labels used by textile manufacturers to identify their materials.
10408227
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, April 16, 2018
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, April 23, 2018
Scope and Contents
Collection consists of the labels used by textile manufacturers to identify their materials. These labels range from simple identification tags to works of art. At their simplest the labels are little more than blank pieces of paper on which the manufacturer, type of cloth, and yardage can be written. The illustrated labels can be anything from simple line drawings to elaborate works of late-19th and early-20th century art, both serious and whimsical.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6524/001: ATHM Textile Industry Documents 6524/002 P: ATHM Textile Industry Photographs 6524/004 G: ATHM Textile Industry Graphics 6524/005 P: ATHM Textile Industry Postcards 6524/006 P: ATHM Textile Industry Stereographs 6524/007 MB: ATHM Textile Industry Memorabilia 6524/008 LS: ATHM Textile Industry Glass Lantern Slides 6524/009 F: ATHM Textile Industry Film 6524/010 AV: ATHM Textile Industry Audio-Visual Materials 6524/011 PUBS: ATHM Textile Industry Publications 6524/012 mf: ATHM Textile Industry Publications on Microfilm 6524/013 PUBS: ATHM Textile Industry Auction Catalog Collection 6524/014 OH: ATHM Textile Industry Oral History 6609 MB: Diogo Teixeira Collection of Textile Industry Cloth Labels 6690 MB: Helena E. Wright Collection of Textile Industry Cloth Labels 6976 MB: Helen K. Bromm Cloth Labels
Arrangement
Series I: Arranged Alphabetically
Series II: From Bliss, Fabyan & Co.
Series III: Cloth Labels in Scrapbooks
10408227
- Series I: Arranged Alphabetically
  - A (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: A, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents
      N.p., n.d. Black/white. 8.50 x 8.50 cm. (all sides of diamond)
    - Item 2: A, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Red/white; letter surrounded by decorative border. 15.50 x 14.50 cm.
    - Item 3: A, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      W. H. Forbes & Co. Lith. N.p., n.d. Red/gold/black/white; large letter surrounded by decorative border. 16.25 X 13.25 cm.
    - Item 4: A, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Blue/white; letter on plain white background. 10 x 9.50 cm.
    - Item 5: A A, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Red/white; double letter surrounded by decorative border. 16.50 x 12 cm.
    - Item 6: A A, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Red/white/gold/black; double letter surrounded by decorative border. 10 x 11.50 cm.
    - Item 7: A A A Colored Flannels, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      ___ Yds., Middlesex Bleachery & Dye Works,, Somerville, Mass. N.p., n.d. Lithograph; red/white; text with decorative corners. 25.25 x 20.25 cm.
    - Item 8: A A A No. 1 colored flannels, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Yds.___, Middlesex Bleachery and Dye Works, Somerville, Mass. N.p., n.d. Red/white; decorative corners. 25 x 20.25 cm.
    - Item 9: A A A A Pocketings, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Red/white; text surrounded by decorative border. 14.75 x 9.25 cm. (Pocketing is a cotton cloth used for making pockets in clothing)
    - Item 10: A A A A Pant Linings, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Yds.___. N.p., n.d. Four red "A's" with black and red decorative border. 15 x 11.50 cm.
    - Item 11: Improved A A A A Wigans, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Four red "A's" surrounded by black decorative border. N.p., n.d. 14.50 x 19 cm. (Wigan is a cotton fabric converted from lightweight sheetings, usually dyed black or gray and starched; used for interlinings in men's and boy's clothing to give body to th
    - Item 12: A C A, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Black/white; letter in each corner of triangle-shaped label. 13 cm. all sides.
    - Item 13: A M Co., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Trademark. N.p., n.d. Blue/gold/white; diamond shaped with decorative border. 6.50 x 6.50 cm.
    - Item 14: Adams Manufacturing Co. Providence, R.I., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      ca. 1870-1872. C.H. Crosby, Lith. 46 Water St. Boston. Blue/gold/white; Greek key border. 18 x 14 cm.
    - Item 15: R.& H. Adams gauze nettings 8 yards., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      R. & H. Adams Gauze Netting. 8 yards. [New York]: R. & H. Adams, ca. 1864-1882. Gold/black/white; image of fly in center (Reg. U.S. Pat. Office). Diamond shaped, 5 x 7.5 cm.
    - Item 16: Feito para Albert Forster Damon, Philadelphia Adamson, Howie & Co. Pernambuco, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      __yards. ca. 1856-1887. Lithograph; yellow/black; image of steamboat flying American flag. cm. Albert Forster Damon was an American merchant operating out of Pernambuco. He resided in Philadelphia after returning from Brazil. Adamson, Howie & Co. were
    - Item 17: Blue drills., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Agawam Canal Co. Agawam Canal Co., D, Blue Drills, Middlesex Bleachery and Dye Works, Somerville, Mass. West Springfield, Mass.: Agawam Canal Co [Cotton Mill], ca. 1800s. Lithograph; orange/black; text only. 25.5 x 20 cm.
    - Item 18: Albany Knit Goods Co., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      S.L.H., Albany, N.Y. Cost__ Color__ No. 40 lbs__ oz. Albany, N.Y.: Albany Knit Goods, Co., ca. 1880s by Geo. M. Hayes. Image of a flower on a stem with a light blue background. 10x6 cm.
    - Item 19: Albert French Finish Percales, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Style No.__Yds__. N.p., n.d. 6.50 x 8.50 cm.
    - Item 20: Alberton warranted fast colors, blue twills., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Alberton, Md.: Alberton Cotton Mills, ca. 1860. Image of mill buildings on right, with railroad on left and men and women walking around in the foreground. Trees and hills in the background. Image is duplicated on Item 21, in this folder, and Box 6, Fo
    - Item 21: Alberton warranted fast colors, brown twills., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Alberton, Md.: Alberton Cotton Mills, ca. 1860. Image of mill buildings on right, with railroad on left and men and women walking around in the foreground. Trees and hills in the background. Identical to Box 6, Folder 1, Item 4. Image is duplicated on I
    - Item 22: Albion Mills, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Grass Bleached. No.__ Yds.__. N.p., n.d. Gold/red/white; text surrounded by floral border with peacock. 19 x 13.25 cm.
    - Item 23: Alexr. Reid, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      No. 50. N.p., n.d. White/gold; image of mahout and three Western men riding an elephant. 6 x 8.75 cm.
    - Item 24: Alexis Soft Finish Wigans, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      ____ Yds. Pelletreau & Raynor, Lith. Co. 35 & 37 Vesey St. N.Y. White/gold/black; text only; decorative top corners. 14.50 x 11.50 cm. Wigans are a cotton fabric converted from lightweight sheetings and print cloths, usually dyed black or gray, starch
    - Item 25: Alexandria Cotton, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Images of pyramids, camels, Egyptian monuments in center; brown and gold background colors. 19.25 x 24.25 cm.
    - Item 26: All Wool Henrietta, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Qte__, Case__, Yds.__, Coulr.__. N.p., n.d. Black/white/silver; text only. 7 x 8.75 cm. Henrietta is a soft, lustrous dress fabric made with silk warp and fine botany worsted filling, or all botany.
    - Item 27: Allison Mills, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      F [in center of label]. N.p., n.d. Lithograph; bright blue with gold lettering and border. 20 x 15.75 cm. (trimmed)
    - Item 28: 1/8 Yd. Allowed, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Black/white; circular label with text only. 2.25 centimeters (dimension)
    - Item 29: Allston Superior Twilled Linings, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Blue/gold/white; text only in oval border. 11.50 x 14 cm. Identical to Item 30, in this folder, except for colors.
    - Item 30: Allston Superior Twilled Linings, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Red/gold/white; text in oval border. 11 x 13.50 cm. Identical to Item 29, in this folder, except for colors.
    - Item 31: Alpaca de Beige, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      No 94; 50 1/2 yds. N.p., n.d. Embossed; gold/white/red/green; text in oval border containing grapes and flowers. 7.50 x 11 cm.
    - Item 32: S.B. & Co. American Cambric, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Lithograph by Forbes & Co.; red/blue/white/gold; American flag with company name in oval. 12.50 x 16.50 cm.
    - Item 33: Exhibition of the Industry of All Nations, New York 1853, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      American Print Works, Fall River, Mass. No. __ 40 yds., H.W. Dubois & Co., Lith, Fall River, Mass. Lithograph; black/white; emblem with classical figures in circle surrounded by wording: Exhibition of the Industry of All Nations, New York, 1853; large "A"
    - Item 34: Superfine Premium Bleached American Steam Mills Shirtings, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Gold script and border against dark red background. 22.25 x 15.5 cm.
    - Item 35: Drill Americano, Azul, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      A.H. y Ca. Fabricado por A.H. y Ca. Extra Superior. At bottom: Middlesex Bleachery and Dye Works, Somerville, Mass. N.p.: A. H. y Ca., n.d. Lithograph; orange/black; scroll work in corners. 24 x 20 cm. Similar to Item 36, in this folder.
    - Item 36: Drill Azul cloth label, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      A.H. y Ca. Americano Fabricado. por A.H. y Ca. At bottom: Middlesex Bleachery & Dye Works, Somerville, Mass. N.p.: A.H. y Ca., n.d. Lithograph; orange/black; scroll work in corners. 23.5 x 19.5 cm. Similar to Item 35, in this folder.
    - Item 37: Amish Denim, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Bliss Fabyan label--Bliss, Faybyan & Co. were Boston dry goods commission merchants. Black lettering against red banners; yellow background with red and gold border. 26.25 x 21.5 cm.
    - Item 38: Amoskeag Manufacturing Company's Mills Manchester, N.H., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      ca. 1800s. Engraved? Image of company mills along Merrimack River, with covered bridge across river; several people, along with a horse and wagon in foreground. 25.5 x 19 cm.
    - Item 39: Amoskeag Manufacturing Company clover cloth, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Patn ____ ____ Yds. Manchester, N.H.: Amoskeag Manufacturing Company, n.d. Trade Mark AMG at top, green lettering against white background. 6.75 x 9.5 cm.
    - Item 40: Ancona Printing Company, madder colors, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      David S. Brown & Co., Agents. No.__, 47 yds. Gloucester, N.J.: Ancona Printing Company, ca. 1870s. Engraving; black/white; view of mill. 16 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 41: Androscoggin., 1873; Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Lewiston, Me.: Androscoggin Mills, 1873 [on reverse in ink]. Pink/gold/red/black; coat of arms with wild boar heads; ivy surrounding shield. 8 x 10.5 cm.
    - Item 42: Androscoggin Mills, Lewiston, Maine., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      ca. 1870s. Engraving; gold/black/white; view of mill with people in foreground. 22 x 16.75 cm. Differs from Item 43, in this folder, which has smoke from chimney.
    - Item 43: Androscoggin Mills, Lewiston, Maine., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      ca. 1870s. Engraving; gold/black/white; view of mill with people in foreground. 22 x 16.75 cm. Differs from Item 42, in this folder: no smoke from chimney.
    - Item 44: Androscoggin Mills, Lewiston, Extra Fine., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      ca. 1870s. Gold/white; text with small bouquet of flowers. 15.25 x 16.5 cm. (trimmed)
    - Item 45: Androscoggin Mills, Lewiston, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      N.d. Gold/white; circular with eagle and shield surrounded by scroll work. Diameter, 16 cm.
    - Item 46: Androscoggin satteen jeans., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      ca. 1870s. Gold/white; text with decorative scrolls in corners. 17.5 x 12.75 cm.
    - Item 47: Aniline Fast Black, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Text only on paper. 17.50 x 5 cm.
    - Item 48: Anti Rheumatic, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      ___yds. N.p., n.d. Black/tan; text with decorative scroll work on board. 3 x 5 cm.
    - Item 49: Anti Rheumatic, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      ___yds. N.p., n.d. Black/tan; text with decorative scroll work on board. 3 x 5 cm. Copy 2.
    - Item 50: Arlington Fine Cottons, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Green/gold; Text with floral picture-frame border. 22 x 18.50 cm.
    - Item 51: Arden Blanket, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Black/tan; text on lightweight cardboard with geometric design in center. 10 x 12.50
    - Item 52: Arlington 26 1/2 pillow ticking, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. White/gold/red/black. Text with decorative border of gold, black and red. 19 x 14 cm.
    - Item 53: Arlington Mills Brown, Wood & Kingman selling agents, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Style 2090, Shade__, Yds. Harbor. Lawrence, Mass.: Arlington Mills, ca. 1883-1887. White/gold/blue/green; medallion with dolphinfish twisted around an anchor with motto: "Skill wins favor," also, border of chain and towers. 6 x 8.5 cm.
    - Item 54: Arnold Print Works, North Adams, Mass. Leland, Allen & Bates, New York, Boston & Philadelphia, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      __ Yds. North Adams, Mass.: Arnold Print Works, ca. 1870s. Engraving; Black/tan; image of classical female figure leaning on bolts of cloth with child holding tablet, factories in background. (Leland, Allen & Bates, selling agents). 13.5 x 19 cm. (cam
    - Item 55: Best madder prints, Harvey Arnold & Co. North Adams, Mass., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      __Yds. North Adams, Mass., ca, ca. 1861-1876. Lithograph; gold/black/white; text with decorative border. Harvey Arnold & Co. were commission agents for Arnold Printworks and other cotton mills in western Mass. 10 x 14 cm.
    - Item 56: Atlantic Co. silecia extra finish for tailors use., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Lawrence, Mass.: Atlantic Cotton Co., ca. 1860. Gold/white/red; text with scroll work; medallion at top with view of Boston harbor and text reading: Bostonia, Condita A.D 1630. Silecia is a cotton lining fabric, highly lustrous with glazed finish; varian
    - Item 57: Atlantic Cotton Mills 72x90 torn., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Macon, GA: Atlantic Cotton MIlls, n.d. White/blue/gold; circular label with image of leopard. 5 cm. diameter.
    - Item 58: Atlantic Mills superior cambrics., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      F.F. Oakleys [Oakley], Lith., Washington St., Boston. Lawrence, Mass.: Atlantic Mills, ca. 1860. Lithograph; black/white; text and image of paddle steamer surrounded by floral border. 16.5 x 13 cm.
    - Item 59: Atlas Brand, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Pure Mohair, Unequalled for Brilliancy & Color. Both Sides Alike, Best Fast Black. No.__, Yds.__, Entered at Stats. Hall. [London]. N.p., n.d. Lithograph; pink/blue/green/gold; text and image showing global view of North and South America. Probably a
    - Item 60: Auburn Fine Cottons, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      N.p., n.d. Lithograph; black/white; text with decorative border. 17.50 x 12 cm.
    - Item 61: Auburndale Heavy Silesias., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Middlesex Bleachy [Bleachery] & Dye Works, Somerville, Mass. Forbes & Co., Boston. N.p., ca. 1870s. Lithograph; black/white/gold. (Silesia is a highly lustrous, glazed finish, cotton lining fabric). 8 x 12 cm.
    - Item 62: New Mills, Avondale, No. ...Yds., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 1)
      [L.] Rosenthal's Lith. S.E. Cor.3rd & Dock St., Philadelphia, Pa., ca. 1860. Image of early mill in Avondale, Pa.; three-story building with cupola on roof and various outbuildings, a home, and school? with flag; a river in foreground with wooden bridge.
  - B, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: B, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      N.p., n.d. White/gold/black. Letter surrounded by decorative border. 11.75 x 14.50 cm.
    - Item 2: B B, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      N.p., n.d. White/gold/black. Double letters surrounded by decorative border. 15 x 12.25 cm.
    - Item 3: B, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      N.p., n.d. Pink/red/gold/white; letter surrounded by decorative border. 11.25 x 13 cm.
    - Item 4: B, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      N.p., n.d. Black/white; circular label; letter surrounded by circular classical border. diameter 7 cm.
    - Item 5: B. H. & Co. Extra Fine Cambric, Superior Finish, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Lithograph; gold/white; text with floral decorations. 9.50 x 12.75 cm.
    - Item 6: B. S. L. Co. Sur Fine, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Blue and gold on white. "W" at each end.
    - Item 7: Men's Egyptian Balbriggan Drawers, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Superior Fabric and Finish. No. 174DS, Size 34, 1/2 dozen. Tan/black; long narrow label with text and scroll work. 18 x 3.50 cm. Balbriggan is a plain stitch knitted fabric used for underwear, sleeping garments, etc.; originally hosiery after the town o
    - Item 8: Ballardvale superfine long cloth Providence R.I., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Entered according to Act of Congress A.D. 1867, by J.B. Altemus..Dist. of Penn. Lithograph; various colors; image of three 19th century hunters on horseback with pack of dogs. 23.25 x 19 cm. J.B. Altemus was dry goods commission agent or selling agent
    - Item 9: Balmoral Skirt, 144 x 44, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      N.p., ca. 1860. Engraving; black/white; woman dressed in Balmoral skirt holding flowers in hand.. 8.75 x 11.75 cm.
    - Item 10: Balmoral Skirts, 144 x 44, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      N.p., ca. 1860. Engraving; black/white; young woman with short Balmoral skirt holding flower in hand; decorative border. 8.50 x 12.50 cm.
    - Item 11: Balmoral Skirt, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      H. Fyfe & Son, 144 inches wide, 43 inches deep. N.p., ca. 1860. Engraving; black/white; young woman in Balmoral skirt. 8 x 11.50 cm.
    - Item 12: Balmoral Skirt, No. 36, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      N.p., ca. 1860. Lithograph; red/white/black/blue; young woman ice-skating in Balmoral skirt. 9.50 x 13 cm.
    - Item 13: McAleese & Johnson's balmoral skirt. 44 X 144., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Entered according to Act of Congress in the the year 1866, by McAleese & Johnson, in the Clerks Office of the District Court, for the Eastern District of Pennsylvania. Philadelphia?, 1866. Engraving; black/white/red; man and woman arm-in-arm; woman weari
    - Item 14: Bang up., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Forbes & Co., Lith., Boston. Entered according to Act of Congress 1868 by W. H. Forbes in the Clerk's Office of the District Court of the District of Mass. N.p., 1868. Lithograph; red/black/yellow/white; image of four cherubs firing a cannon. 11.5 x 15
    - Item 15: Barbour's hand spun., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Barbour Flax Spinning Co. Barbour's Hand Spun Flax. Paterson, N.J.: Barbour Flax Spinning Co., n.d. Blue/white/red; image of red hand, word "flax" on palm (probably a play on the company's origins in Ulster, Ireland); hand is surrounded by shamrocks and
    - Item 16: Barkammu Da Ganinka., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      With Arabic script. Manchester, Eng., ca. 1900. Lithograph; blue/gold/ red/green/yellow; image of Muslim men and boys worshiping in mosque; figure [Mohammad?] with sword pointing to Arabic script. 16.5 x 22 cm.
    - Item 17: Bartlet Steam Mills fine cottons., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      W.H. Forbes Lith. Boston. Newburyport, Mass., ca.1870s. Lithograph; red/gold/white/black; text with decorative scrollwork. (often spelled as Bartlett) 17.5 X 13.5 cm.
    - Item 18: Bartlet Steam Mills, Newburyport., Improved Long Cloths, Wessacumcon, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Lith. of C. H. Crosby, Boston. Newburyport, Mass.: Bartlet Steam Mills, ca. 1870s. Lithograph; gold/red/tan; American Indian in center with bow and arrows; scroll with "Ense Petit Placidam Sub Libertate Quietem," scrollwork and flowers border. Longclo
    - Item 19: Bartlet Steam Mills, Fine Cottons, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      W.H. Forbes & Co. Lith. Newburyport, Mass.: Bartlet Steam Mills, ca. 1870s. Lithograph; green/gold; text with scrollwork border. (Bartlet often spelled Bartlett). 20.5 x 14 cm.
    - Item 20: Bates Mills, Lewiston, Maine., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      N.d. Lithograph; blue/white/black; text with elaborate scrollwork border. 13 x 17 cm.
    - Item 21: Bates Mills, Extra Heavy Cottons, 2 1/2 Yards Wide, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Lewiston, Maine. Lewiston, Me.: Bates Mills, n.d. Lithograph; blue/gold/red/white; text with flowers and scrollwork. 20.5 x 15 cm.
    - Item 22: Notice! Notice! This company having remodeled their mill have adopted a new ticket and trade mark..., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Bay Mill. .. signed A. Hill Treas. (Probably Albert Hill, son of Bay Mill founder Thomas Jefferson Hill), Providence, R.I.: Bay Mill, ca. 1870-1875, Image of a treasury bank note style w/portrait of woman. American BankNote Co. New York at bottom. 9 x
    - Item 23: Beach Dale Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      N.p., n.d. Lithograph; green/red/white; text with wide scrollwork border. (Sometimes spelled Beachdale). 16 x 14 cm. Very similar to Item 24, in this folder.
    - Item 24: Beach Dale Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Middlesex Bleachery and Dye Works, Middlesex Bleachery and Dye Works,, Somerville, Mass. N.p., n.d. LIthograph; green, red, white; text with decorative scrollwork. (Sometimes spelled Beachdale). 16 x 14 cm. Very similar to Item 23, in this folder.
    - Item 25: Beachdale Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Middlesex Bleachery and Dye Works,, Somerville, Mass. N.p., n.d. Lithograph; blue/gold/maroon/white; text with decorative scrollwork. (Sometimes spelled Beach Dale). 11.50 x 15.50 cm.
    - Item 26: Beaman corset jeans., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      West Boylston, Mass.: Beaman Manufacturing Company, ca. 1850s. Image of mill complex in center background; wagon and people standing on edge of river in foreground. 20 x 15 cm.
    - Item 27: Beaman Blue Drills Warranted Indigo Blue, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Yds. West Boylston, Mass.: Beaman Manufacturing Company, ca. 1860. Black lettering and frame against orange background. 25 x 20.5 cm.
    - Item 28: Beaman Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      West Boylston, Mass.: Beaman Manufacturing Company, ca. 1850s. Image of mill complex in center background; wagon and people standing on edge of river in foreground. Black lettering and decoration against yellow background. Identical to Item 29, in this
    - Item 29: Beaman Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)
      West Boylston, Mass.: Beaman Manufacturing Company, ca. 1850s. Image of mill complex in center background; wagon and people standing on edge of river in foreground. Black lettering and decoration against pink background. Identical to Item 28, in this f
    - Item 30: Beaman Mills., Cloth label (Box 1, Folder 2)